Guide to the Residential College Seminar Program, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Residential College Seminar Program records, 1993-2002; Accession 2007-A-006
  - BK [Berkeley]
    - Mitchell-Loretan, Laura -BK/PC 433a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Ammarell, Eugene -BK/SM 442b, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - BR [Branford]
    - Reiss, Diana -BR/ES -Fall, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Reiss, Diana -CSES/CC 394a -Fall, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Kellert, Priscilla -BR/BK 441b, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - CC [Calhoun]
  - Sherman, Jonathan -CC/DC 431a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - DC [Davenport] -no primary seminars
  - TD [Timothy Dwight]
    - Bartow, Joanna -TD/SM 430a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Bresnick, Adam -TD/DC 432a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Weiss, James -TD/CC 433a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Sorkin, Jerome -TD/CC 442b, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Weiss, James -CSES/CSSM 344b, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Weiss, James -CSJE/ES 324b, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - JE [Jonathan Edwarda]
    - Mehta, Linn -JE/CC 430a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Bai, Qianshen -JE/ES 440b, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - MC [Morse]
    - Anker, Andrew with David Perkes -MC/TC 430a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Keys, Gary -MC/SM 431a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Keys, Gary -CSMC/SM 416a, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Bengston, Carla -Mc/SY 440b, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - PC [Pierson]
    - Myers, Morey -PC/SY -Fall, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Myers, Morey -CSDC/SM 390a, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Myers, Morey -JE/ES 352a, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Myers, Morey -CSMC/CSTD 304a, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Myers, Morey -CSTD/PC 471a, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Haase, Leif -PC/BK 440b, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - SY [Saybrook]
    - Schlager, Bernard -SY/JE 431a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Schlager, Bernard -CSBR/TC 410a, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Shteir, Rachel -SY/BR 432a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Piemontese-Ramos, Luisa -SY/MC 441b, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Stepanek, James -SY/DC 443b, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Stepanek, James -CSDC/SY 363b, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - ES [Ezra Stiles]
    - Crowley, John -ES/JE 435a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Palwick, Susan -ES/CC 432a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Ribe, Neil -ES/SY 403a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Ribe, Neil -CSES 364b, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Ribe, Neil -CSES 294b, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Ribe, Neil -CSES/CSDC 273a, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - TC [Trumbull]
    - Barker-Kline, Christina -TC/BK 431a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Barker-Kline, Christina -CSTD/SY -Fall, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Dana, Catherine -TC/BR 433a, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Belsey, Erika -TC/TD 440b, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Moore, Susanna -TC/BR 442b, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Moore, Susanna -CSSY/TD 3 61b, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Moore, Susanna -CSES/CSTC 346b, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Residential College Seminars [course catalogues] Fall 1994 and Spring 1995, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - BK [Berkeley]
    - Morrison, Jennifer -BK/MC 450a, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Simmons, Robert -BK/JE 451a, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Einsfeld, Nancy -BK/TC 461b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - BR [Branford]
    - Cape, Tony -BR/PC 450a, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Bowman, Jeffrey -BR/DC 460b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Kirschner, Bryan et al. -BR/SM 461b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - CC [Calhoun]
    - Walbert, Kate -CC/TD 451a, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Walbert, Kate -CSMC/PC -Fall, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Walbert, Kate -CSSM/MC 372a, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Marks, Jonathan -CC/DD462b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Marks, Jonathan -JE/CC 423b, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - DC [Davenport]
    - Lane, Joshua -DC/SM 452a, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Kalinowska-Blackwood, Izabela -TD/JE 450a, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Levitsky, Jonathan -TD/SM 460b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Mufson, Dan -TD/BR 462b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Smith, John -TD/TC 465b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - JE [Jonathan Edwards]
    - Schleifer, James -JE/BK 464b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Schleifer, James -CSES/CSDC 275a, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Schleifer, James -CSDC 255a, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - MC [Morse]
    - Organschi, Alan & Elizabeth Gray -MC/ES 451a, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Singer, Dorothy -MC/TC 453a, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Valenti, F. Miguel -MC/SM 464b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Valenti, F. Miguel -SM/BR 440b, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Zucker, John -PC/DC 451a, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Ganassi, Ian -PC/SY462b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Paris, Jonathan -DC/TD 463b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Paris, Jonathan -PC/DC 442b, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - SY [Saybrook]
    - Smith, Suzanne -SY/BK 452a, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Smith, Suzanne -CSMC/PC 412a, 1992-1993 (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Jannuzi, Frank -SY/DC 461b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Rosenthal, Steven -SY/PC 460b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Rosenthal, Steven -CSCC/SY 381b, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Thompson, Leonard -SY/TC 463b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Thompson, Leonard -SY/TC 444b, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - SM [Silliman] no primary seminars
  - ES [Ezra Stiles]
    - Greenfield, Matthew -ES/SY 453a, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Dembo, Joseph -ES/TC 460b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Dembo, Joseph -CSTC/PC -Fall, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Dembo, Joseph -CSBR 191b, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Ramos, Jr., Valeriano -ES/SM 462b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Ramos, Jr., Valeriano -CSPC/JE 406b, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Vakil, Cyrus -ES/BK 463b, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Vakil, Cyrus -CSJE/SY 382b, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - TC [Trumbull] no primary seminars
  - Residential College Seminars [course catalogues] Fall 1995 and Spring 1996, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - BK [Berkeley]
    - Weissberg, Melissa -BK/JE 472a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Weissberg, Melissa -JE/SY 434a, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Weissberg, Melissa -CSJE/CC -Fall, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Gardiner, Gale -BK/SY 482b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Gardiner, Gale -TC/JE 462b, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Grose, Peter -BK/MC 481b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Seybold, Nancy -BK/TD 480b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Seybold, Nancy -ES/SY 442b, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Br [Branford]
    - Schupack, Deborah -BR/CC 480b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - CC [Calhoun]
    - Parisier, Nicole -CSCC/SY 472a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Riobo, Carlos -CC/DC 482b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - DC [Davenport]
    - Worth, Alexi -DC/JE 481b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - TD [Timothy Dwight]
    - Green-McCreight, Kathryn -TD/SY 483b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - JE [Jonathan Edwards]
    - Matz, Jesse -CSJE/BR 471a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Bolanos, Henry -CS/JE 470a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Lee, Daryl -JE/ES 484b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - MC [Morse]
    - Aaboe, Asgar -CSMC/TC 470a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Hubbell, Andrea -CSMC/BR 472a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Hubbell, Andrea -CC/PC 452a, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Saul, Jamie -MC/MC 480b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Saul, Jamie -BK 443b, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - PC [Pierson]
    - Bowen, Ezra -PC/JE 482b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Bowen, Ezra -BK/TC 452a, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Bowen, Ezra -TD/BC 431a, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Bowen, Ezra -CSSY/PC 391a, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - Bowen, Ezra -CSTD/CSSY 296b, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Bowen, Ezra -CSTD 87b, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Bowen, Ezra -SM 73a & b, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Collins, Kevin -PC/BR 481b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 120)
  - SY [Saybrook]
    - Geddes, Raymond -CSSY/DC 471a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 121)
  - SM [Silliman]
    - Carroll, Peter -CSSM/SY 470a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Rogers, Naomi -CSSM/ES 471a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Spiesel, Christina -CSSM/ES 472a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Spiesel, Christina -TC/PC 441b, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Spiesel, Christina -TC/PC 421b, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Spiesel, Christina -CSTC/BK 392a, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Spiesel, Christina -CSTC/BK 352a, 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Spiesel, Christina -CSSY/CSMC 336a, 1988-1989 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Spiesel, Christina -CSBK/CSCC 305a, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 130)
    - Spiesel, Christina -CSTC/CSTD 287a, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 131)
    - Spiesel, Christina -CSTC/CSBR 251a, 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 132)
    - Spiesel, Christina -CSBK 230a, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 133)
    - Lapadula, Marc -SM/TC 483b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 134)
    - Lapadula, Marc -PC/CC 461b, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 135)
    - Lapadula, Marc -CSTD/MC 426b, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 136)
    - Lapadula, Marc -CSMC 400b, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 137)
    - McNutt, Jenny L. -SM/TD 482b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 138)
    - McNutt, Jenny L. -CC/TD 420b, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 139)
  - ES [Ezra Stiles]
    - Baldwin, Douglas -CSES/BK 470a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 140)
    - Baldwin, Douglas -MC/JE 442b, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 141)
    - McColgan, Denise -ES/BR 481b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 142)
    - Esty, Joshua -ES/DC 480b, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 143)
    - Esty, Joshua -TC/BR 451a, 1994-1995 (Box 3, Folder 144)
  - TC [Trumbull]
    - Weisser, Amy -CSTC/MC 471a, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 145)
    - Weisser, Amy -CSTC/JE 404b, 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 146)
  - Residential College Seminars [course catalogues] Fall 1996 and Spring 1997, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges: College Seminars -Fall Term, 1996 -General Information (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Proposed College Seminars: Spring Term 1997 (Box 4, Folder 154)
  - BK [Berkeley]
    - Rotskoff, Lori -BK/SM 311a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Weicker, Lowell -YC 310a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Tripp, Tripp -BK/PC 322b, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 157)
  - BR [Branford]
    - Steiner, Emily -BR/TC 321b, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 158)
  - CC [Calhoun]
    - Martinelli, Tom -CC/BR 311a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Salinas, Shannon -CC/BK 312a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 160)
  - DC [Davenport]
    - Howe, Roger -DC/JE 310a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Howe, Roger -CSDC 217b, 1981-1982 (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Stark, Barbara -DC/MC 311a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Stark, Barbara -CSBK/CC 471a, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 164)
    - Vallianatos, Evan -DC/TC 312a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 165)
    - Ahdieh, Robert -DC/PC 320b, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 166)
  - TD [Timothy Dwight]
    - Kostalevsky, Marina -TD/SY 310a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 167)
    - Kostalevsky, Marina -JE/MC 443b, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 168)
  - JE [Jonathan Edwards]
    - Feldman, Noah -JE/BR 312a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 169)
  - MC [Morse]
    - Levine, Caroline -MC/DC 321b, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 170)
  - PC [Pierson]
    - Cowlin, Ann -PC/DC 313a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 171)
    - Cowlin, Ann -TC/SM 432a, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 172)
  - SY [Saybrook]
    - Clarkson, Ginger -SY/BK 314a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 173)
    - Clarkson, Ginger -CSJE/SM 425b, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 174)
    - Clarkson, Ginger -TD/JE 452a, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 175)
    - Clarkson, Ginger -CSJE/DC 372a, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 176)
    - Clarkson, Ginger -CSJEMC 350a, 1989-1990 (Box 4, Folder 177)
    - Lee, Marie -SY/TD 312a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 178)
    - Cobb, Christopher -SY/CC 321b, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 179)
  - SM [Silliman]
    - Tymowski, Andrzej -SM/BK 313a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 180)
    - Tymowski, Andrzej -CSDC/PC 473a, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 181)
    - Tymowski, Andrzej -CSBR 298b, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 182)
    - Tymowski, Andrzej -CSTC 270a, 1984-1985 (Box 4, Folder 183)
    - Wiseman, Geoffrey -SM/SY 320b, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 184)
  - ES [Szra Stiles]
    - Schwab, Eric -ES/PC 314a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 185)
    - Duffy, Dan -ES/BK 321b, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 186)
    - Michaelson, Jay -ES/TD 320b, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 187)
    - Wu, King-lui -ES/BR 323b, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 188)
    - Wu, King-lui -ES 464b, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 189)
    - Wu, King-lui -ES/JE 439a, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 190)
    - Wu, Kig-lui -CSES/BK 381b, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 191)
    - Wu, King-lui -CSES/CC -Fall, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 192)
    - Wu, King-lui -CSES 319a, 1987-1988 (Box 4, Folder 193)
    - Wu, King-lui -CSES 305a, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Wu, King-lui -CSES 243b, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 195)
  - TC [Trumbull]
    - Wetzsteon, Rachel -TC/JE 314a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Burnett, D. Graham -ES/JE 313a, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Burnett, Graham & Aaron Hirsch -TC/ES 322b, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 198)
  - Residential College Seminars [course catalogues] Fall 1997 and Spring 1998, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 199)
  - Committee on Teaching in the Residential Colleges: College Seminars -Fall Term, 1997 -General Information (Box 5, Folder 200)
  - BK [Berkeley]
    - Modlin, Irvin -CSBK/PC 330a, [file retained by office, 2/22/2008], 1997-1998 (Box 5)
    - Freiman, Jonathan -BK/BR 342b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Johnson, Robert -BK/TC 340b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 203)
  - BR [Branford]
    - Goff-Crews, Kimberly -CSBR/DC 331a, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Goff-Crews, Kimberly -CC/BK 312a, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - DeCherney, Peter -CSBR/MC 343b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 206)
  - CC [Calhoun]
    - Weber, Katherine -CSCC/SM 331a, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Levey, Jane and Lori Rotskoff -CC/CC 342b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Walsh, Brendan -CC/TD 341b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 209)
  - DC [Davenport]
    - Boyland, Christine -CSDC/MC 330a, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Hsu, Mary Li -CSDC/SM 341b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 211)
  - TD [Timothy Dwight]
    - Dawson, Daniel -CSTD/ES 331a, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Southward, David -CSTD/BR 330a, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Mahallati, Mohammed -TD/DC 342b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Shah, Samir & Max Kelz -TD/TC 343b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Shah, Samir & Max Kelz -CC/SM 322b, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 216)
  - JE [Jonathan Edwards]
    - Carter, James -CSJE/TC 331a, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Pollvogt, Susanah -JE/DC 343b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 218)
  - MC [Morse]
    - Kotuk, Richard -CSMC/BK 331a, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Kotuk, Richard -TC/TD 311a, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Travis, Trysh -CSMC/C 333a, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Chessman, Harriet Scott -MC/JE 341b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Standard, Michael -MC/SY 42b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Standard, Michael -BK/JE 20b, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 224)
  - PC [Pierson]
    - Mutchler, J.C. -CSPC/SY 320a (withdrawn by instructor 6/97), 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Mutchler, J.C. -CC/MC -- Spring, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Baligh, Randa -PC/SM 342b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 227)
  - ES [Ezra Stiles]
    - Sze, Sarah -ES/PC 343b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 228)
  - SY [Saybrook]
    - Moskowitz, Marina -CSSY/PC 331a, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - Kirchwey, Karl -SY/ES 340b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 230)
  - SM [Silliman]
    - Feldman, Barbara -CSSM/SY 330a, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - Feldman, Barbara -SM/CC 481b, 1995-1996 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - Feldman, Barbara -SY/CC 450a, 1994-1995 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Feldman, Barbara -CSJE/BK 427b, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Feldman, Barbara -CSSM/JE 394a, 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Feldman, Barbara -CSBR/TC 365b, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Feldman, Barbara -CSPC/DC 341b, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Feldman, Barbara -CSES/CSMC 317a, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Feldman, Barbara -CSSY/CSCC 293a, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Feldman, Barbara -CSMC/CSTD 273a, 1984-1985 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Feldman, Barbara -CSMC/CSTD 239b, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Feldman, Barbara -CSES 196b, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Johnson, Brian -SM/SY 343b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Johnson, Brian -PC/SY 323b, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - Osofski, Hari -SM/PC 344b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 245)
  - TC [Trumbull]
    - Gordon, Joy -TC/SY 341b, 1997-1998 (Box 5, Folder 246)
  - Residential College Seminars [course catalogues] Fall 1998 and Spring 1999, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 249)
  - BK [Berkeley]
    - Robin, Corey -CSBK/BR 364b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 250)
  - BR [Branford]
    - Saiber, Arielle -CSBR/ES 352a, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - Karem, Frederick -CSBR/TC 362b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 252)
  - CC [Calhoun]
    - Kimmelman, Jonathan -CSCC/BK 362b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - Papenfuse, Eric -CSCC/SY 360b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 254)
  - DC [Davenport]
    - Bang, Mary Jo -CSDC/MC 350a, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 255)
    - Bang, Mary Jo -CSTC/ES 330a, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - Yow, Laura -CSDC/JE 362b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 257)
  - TD [Timothy Dwight]
    - Zucker, Rachel -CSTD/PC 351a, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 258)
    - Zucker, Rachel -BR/MC 322b, 1996-1997
    - Livingston, Jennie -CSTD/MC 362b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 259)
    - Lobel, Michael -CSTD/BK 361b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 260)
  - JE [Jonathan Edwards]
    - Gonzalez, Gaspar -CSJE/CC 352a, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 261)
  - MC [Morse]
    - Isenberg, Steven -CSMC/DC 363b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - Jacoby, Jeff [rejected by CTRC for F98], 1998 (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - PC [Pierson] no primary seminars
  - SY [Saybrook]
    - Foster, Karen -CSSY/TD 350a, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Gartner, David -CSSY/DC 351a, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - Sellar, Tom -CSSY/PC 352a, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 266)
  - SM [Silliman]
    - Posel, Ben -CSSM/DC 352a, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - Posel, Ben -CSTD/BK 332a, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 268)
    - Balmain, Melissa -CSSM/ES 364b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Lee, Susanna -CSSM/BR 363b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Suk, Jeannie -CSSM/JE 361b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 271)
  - ES [Ezra Stiles]
    - Hill, Richard -CSES/BR 351a, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 272)
    - Hill, Richard -CSTC/BR 393a, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - Hill, Richard -CSMC/PC 363b, 1989-1990 (Box 6, Folder 274)
    - Hill, Richard -CSSY/TD 324b, 1987-1988 (Box 6, Folder 275)
    - Hill, Richard -CSES 297b, 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 276)
    - Hill, Richard -CSJE/CSBK 249b, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 277)
    - Hill, Richard -CSES/CSBR 231a, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - Dubman, Jonathan -CSES/TC 363b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 279)
    - Gudis, Catherine -CSES/CC 365b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 280)
  - TC [Trumbull]
    - Lord, George -CSTC/ES 361b, 1998-1999 (Box 6, Folder 281)
    - Lord, George -TC/JE -Spring, 1978-1998 (Box 6, Folder 282)
    - Lord, George -CSTC/TC -Fall, 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 283)
    - Lord, George -CSTC/TC 391a, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 284)
    - Lord, George -CSTC 255a, 1983-1984 (Box 6, Folder 285)
  - Residential College Seminars [course catalogue] Fall 1999 (Box 7, Folder 286)
  - BK [Berkeley]
    - Lowe, Celia -CSBK 371a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - Rosenzweig, Jane Ann -CSBK 373a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - Hartman, Karen -CSBK 381b (DC), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - Hartman, Karen -CSTC/SM 351a, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - Hartman, Karen -BR/CC 310a, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - BR [Branford]
    - Paik, Young-Jay -CSBR 371a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 292)
  - CC [Calhoun]
    - Anderson, Michael -CSCC 370a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 293)
    - Anderson, Michael -CC/BR 340b, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 294)
  - DC [Davenport]
    - Hillman, Elizabeth -CSDC 371a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - Mohaptra, Kailish -CSDC 384b (BK), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - Mohaptra, Kailish -CSSY/CC 363b, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 297)
  - TD [Timothy Dwight]
    - Bloom, Harold -CSTD 370a (JE), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 298)
    - Bloom, Harold -CSTD/TD 353a, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 299)
    - Jannarone, Kimberly -CSTD 371a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - Beskin, Lisa -CSTD 380b (CC), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - Kroger, John -CSTD 381b (SY), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - Kroger, John -CSCC/TC 332a, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 303)
  - JE [Jonathan Edwards]
    - Cheever, Susan -CSJE 372a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 304)
    - Zucker, Rachel -CSJE 380b (SY), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 305)
  - MC [Morse]
    - Farrell, Gordon -CSMC 382b (TD), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 306)
    - Farrell, Gordon -CSJE/MC 351a, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 307)
    - Farrell, Gordon -CC/JE 460b, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 308)
    - Farrell, Gordon -ES/BR 430a, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 309)
    - Farrell, Gordon -CSPC/SY 402b, 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 310)
    - Farrell, Gordon -BSPC/BR 382b, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 311)
  - PC [Pierson]
    - Barnhart, Catherine -CSPC 373a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 312)
    - Norchi, Charles -CSPC 371a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - Norchi, Charles -CC/TD 425b, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - Norchi, Charles -CSCC/SM 366b, 1989-1990 (Box 7, Folder 315)
    - Norchi, Charles -CSJE/CSTC 336a, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - Norchi, Charles -CSJE/CC 328b, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - Austin, Nancy -CSPC/TD 363b, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 318)
    - Bilston, Sarah -CSPC 380b (MC), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 319)
    - McGill, Scott & Joseph Luzzi -CSPC 382b (BK), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 320)
    - Soutter, Lucy -CSPC 383b (CC), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 321)
  - SY [Saybrook]
    - Jucovy, Timothy -CSSY 372a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 322)
    - Parlow, Matthew -CSSY 382b (ES), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 323)
  - SM [Silliman]
    - Sleeper, James -CSSM 370a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 324)
    - Underwood, Thomas -CSSM 383b (SY), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 325)
    - Underwood, Thomas -CSPC/ES 362b, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 326)
    - Underwood, Thomas -CSSM/JE 333a, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 327)
    - Underwood, Thomas -BK/JE 483b, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 328)
    - Underwood, Thomas -CSBK/JE 472a, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 329)
    - Underwood, Thomas -ES/CC 443b, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 330)
  - ES [Ezra Stiles]
    - Boothby, Derek -CSES 381b (MC), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 331)
    - Boothby, Derek -CSTC/MC 364b, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 332)
    - Hotstetter, Margaret -CSES 383b (MC), 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 333)
    - Hotstetter, Margaret -CSES/BK 360b, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 334)
    - Mettitzki, Dorothee -CSES 370a, 1999-2000 (Box 7, Folder 335)
    - Metlitzki, Dorothee -ES/TD -- Spring, 1997-1998 (Box 7, Folder 336)
    - Metlitzki, Dorothee -ES/JE 324b, 1996-1997 (Box 7, Folder 337)
    - Metlitzki, Dorothee -ES/CC 483b, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 338)
    - Metlitzki, Dorothee -ES/MC 438a, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 339)
    - Metlitzki, Dorothee -ES/BR 438a, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 340)
    - Metlitzki, Dorothee -CSES/SM 411a, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 341)